Fiverr 5 is back and we also got a
little surprise from the little brother
Sonnet 5. And
if you read the timeline, it's a good
model or it's like expensive. So, we're
going to discuss about that because
yeah, I'm I'm not sure. Is that really
the model that everyone was expecting?
Probably not, but we got it. We're going
to use it.
Fiverr 5 will come back soon enough so
we can burn even more token. How is that
going to match on our workflow
automation and workflow that we have set
up? We are going to see that in that
video. But okay, so first the little
brother Sonnet 5. Okay, so same design,
same logo. Okay, that's cool. Which is
Okay, that I like.
The benchmark again for Sonnet 5 against
4.8.
That's cool because it's almost the same
thing and
from 4.6 to 5, we got from object candy
like the terminal bench 2.1 from 67 to
80%. That's a lot. That's insane.
And yeah, though the benchmark Okay,
it's a lot whatever computer use cool
and knowledge work. Yeah, knowledge work
it's even above 4.8.
>> Yeah, but just a little little bit.
Yeah. Nothing too big, but
>> But the pricing 4.8 is five in
and
>> 25 out.
And Sonnet 5 Okay, so until August 31st
>> Mhm.
>> two in and 10 out
for the same benchmark.
>> Yeah.
That's that's a lot cheaper.
>> And after that, it's going to do
>> 50%
>> 50% on top.
>> Yeah.
So,
>> by September 1st, we will have like
Sonnet 7 if it's going this pace.
>> Yeah, it could be too.
But yeah, like
it's for now. That's That's great. And I
mean, okay, so that's the price of the
the model itself, but
>> What is the difference in price with the
previous on it?
Or the 4.6?
>> Yes.
>> How much more expensive did they make
it?
>> 4.6, so three in and 15 out. What?
>> Yeah, that's the that's the same price
for five, so you can just update your
API to five and pay nothing additional.
>> Yeah, it's haven't Yeah,
okay.
>> Because of the discount they give you.
>> Yes.
>> So, if you have an API, update it. Put
it on five.
>> We did. But, also uh
that's the pricing per token, but it
depends of the how many token the model
is using to do a task.
>> Yes.
>> So, yeah, because Acul is like one in
and five out, but I know I never use
Acul. Like it uh for with open clue,
Acul was just to do the head bit.
>> Well, I tried it and it gave me such bad
results that I skipped it after 30
minutes of testing.
>> I know exactly. Like nobody's using Acul
whatsoever, right? But, again, like
yeah, if you have a big task with Sony
and it take less token to use, then it
can be even cheaper than some open
source model that are way cheaper per
token, but it's take 45 minutes to do a
task that it will take 5 minutes to do
Sony and burn like 10 times more tokens.
So, yeah, those those benchmark are
tricky and it needs to be output based.
But, how do you measure the output
anyway? Codex, I'm fighting against
uh once the session is done, open a pull
request, commit, push, and pull request.
And Claude is
today wiped out my work trees.
I said, "Oh, yeah, clean those work
trees in that project." And he cleaned
he went to clean the other project, too.
And then he said, "Hey, bro, what the
fuck?"
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, I had some spare time and spare
tokens, so I did everything.
>> Exactly.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah. So, it's still tricky, but like
we're getting really, really powerful
models. Like, do you have a look at the
code anymore? Still?
>> I do at the end. I check it.
>> Okay.
>> But, I still do even I don't only use
Opus for reviewing. I still have Codex
5.5 finding issues that Codex that Opus
doesn't find.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah, I mean, like both
models are good working together. Like,
again, so
this week I've So, I
I kept set up those automation in Codex
and the cloud desktop app.
So, now I have implementation like
features implementation taking from
GitHub every 2 hours. And
[clears throat] I have a pull request
review every 6 hours. And then it's
merged to master. And I'm I'm about to
put auto deploy to production later this
week, maybe. And because yeah, okay,
green up, so it's different. But, uh so
there is that. And I also have like a
routine of refactoring and dry the code
because that we have a lot of slope in
the app. So, those those routine are
required. But, uh yeah, it's good. And I
didn't burn my cloud subscription in 2
days this time. So, that's a win. Max
effort Sony works harder than previous
Anthropic model. It used 40% more output
token per okay. And 3x the agentic
stones for knowledge work evaluation.
Yeah, okay, [snorts] that's not See,
that's Axel. That's why it's not that
cheap.
>> No.
>> Yeah. I mean, maybe it's because of the
launch.
Could find thing those
what they could find thing post training
on the Entropic side, but yeah.
>> Yeah, like
I mean, if we get more than it is, I
don't know. Like the workflows from 4.8
and Fable 5 that are using in neutral
code mode will be interesting for that
because I
I'm going to build my subscription like
crazy again.
Yeah. I don't know, man. Cloud 2.5 cost
more per task than 4.8 before accounting
for promotional pricing. 2.5 cost 2.29
per task on the intelligence index. A 2x
increase compared to 4.6.
4.6.
Yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> That's a big difference if you compare
it to the chart where it even gives you
a discount at this moment.
>> And 50% more than Cloud Opus 4.8. Yeah,
okay. It's cheaper than Fable 5
basically.
>> Sick.
>> This is driving a 30% increase on token
usage. Yes. Okay, so yes, like the
price per token is cheap cheap or like
same price, but it use more tokens.
That's sad. Token efficiency is so bad,
it end up being more expensive than
Cloud 4.8 Opus 4.8. If And that's what
Theo was also talking about when say
like a OpenAI is focusing on token
efficiency because it's also compute,
right? If Anthropic is [__] up with
those token consumption, no [__] they
don't have enough compute.
>> Yeah, well.
>> But if they fix that, if they are
efficient and they have the smartest
model for coding, etc., that's a banger.
>> The thing is we don't know, right? We
don't know if they need to optimize it
and it will be better later. We don't
know if they just wanted to push and
couldn't push fast enough, so they agree
with using more tokens so that they can
reach the level that they want.
So, if you want to boost like a few
points on on on the comparison on the
benchmark, you can also just let it burn
more tokens and it will be better.
>> Yeah.
Yeah, and I mean like the more token you
use, the more subscription you burn, so
let's go.
>> Yeah. So, the for me the question is to
you, what are you going to do? Keep
using Opus 4.8 or are you using Sonnet 5
by default? Or just say, I use 4.8
UltraCode and have them both.
>> So, yeah, I think for now I'm going to
keep my
workflow that I have right now because
so, the PRD is playing yeah,
by Opus and then it's sent to GitHub.
Then I have those routines that run on
the Codex app that picked up those
tasks, implement them,
and then I have those reviews with 4.8
UltraCode, and then I push everything to
master and I publish. I don't think like
Sonnet 5 would change anything with that
because it still works. It's just like
the split is kind of like cool.
Actually, yeah, maybe I can optimize it
or have different routines
and more actions where the cheapest
model. And if Sonnet 5 is smaller than
4.6, then I I will have a better cleaner
GitHub board.
>> Yeah.
>> So, that's what I like.
I like I like to have clean board.
>> Yes. Have it empty and everything built.
>> Yeah. And I don't We start me reviewing
anything. Yeah. I just in the app on
production and say, "Oh, yeah, it's
broken. Close. Fix it."
>> Yes. When Vincent is offline, make sure
it works when he comes back. I'm sure
I'm going to wait for Fable 5 because
he's going to review everything I've
built in the past few days. But on my
API setup for for that's connecting to
my software,
I'm going to upgrade to Sonnet 5. Just
see what it does and see if I see a peak
or a change in my cost. And if it is
around the same amount, I don't mind.
I'm just keeping a Sonnet 5.
>> Yeah, okay. That makes sense. Mi-
Mitchell, thank you for your time.
And
>> See you next week.
>> Yes, next week. Subscribe, comments,
like, share the video because we need
more
>> Do everything.
>> Thank you.
Bye.
>> Where's the button? Is the button is
here? Bye.